Get up.
Let's go.
Boss.
We're alive today
all thanks to Lord Huo's grace.
Translations for various countries.
Wishing you a prosperous business.
Sir.
I have a very complicated deal here.
I wonder if we can talk about it.
Just say what you want to say, sir.
I can do
any kind of business here.
Forging identities.
Who are you?
I won't do anything that gets me shot.
I'm just here to ask you for some information.
I don't offer that service here.
If you keep this up, I'll call the police.
I am the police.
I wonder if you've seen him.
His name is Huo Qishan.
I've seen him.
He got identities for several countries from me.
Several identities?
I...
Hello.
Siyao.
That old fox Huo Qishan
forged several fake identities.
I think
it's highly unlikely he went to the pier.
We still need to
block all streets leading out of the city.
Huo Qishan won't escape by boat.
Trust me this time.
Send someone to Baixiang Lou immediately.
A brothel?
Baixiang Lou is not a brothel.
Then what is it?
Baixiang Lou has a secret tunnel
that leads directly out of the city.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Is it not to your taste?
You really are scheming.
Who would have thought that at this time
you would still be at your lover's place?
I am who I am today because of my benefactor.
I can do anything for my benefactor.
Ningning,
over the years, I
have done a lot of bad things.
But,
I love you very much.
Love?
Love like yours is worse than killing me.
How about this.
After we get out safely,
we'll start over.
I will definitely be a good man.
Start over?
Don't you think you are being ridiculous?
Since you're not eating,
let's get ready to go.
Yingxiang,
get ready to leave.
Okay.
You won't find Huo Qishan here.
Get in the car.
What's going on?
He escaped through the secret passage.
There's no time to explain.
Get in the car.
Master.
Senior Sister.
Little Bandit.
Please let him go.
I didn't take any of his wealth.
Now,
his life is all he has left.
Ningning.
Where is our money?
What are you doing?
Everything is gone.
Just go.
Never come back.
Never look back.
It's all gone.
You.
Don't shoot.
Don't be impulsive,
Ningning.
Huo Qishan,
isn't everything you've done
for Ningning?
Think of Ningning.
Don't be impulsive.
Huo Qishan,
Ningning is your biological daughter.
Sir,
turn back.
Li Chengrui.
Senior Brother.
Thank you
for still calling me
Senior Brother.
Zhou Wei,
come back.
Ningning,
listen to Daddy
and come with me.
You are not my dad.
Jiang Siyao,
you did all of this.
I...
Dad.
Ningning.
I know you like steamed buns.
Get up and eat them.
Zhou Wei.
I beg you.
Please wake up.
Welcome, Inspector Zhou. You've officially joined
the Phoenix Police Department.
From now on, we'll uphold justice
and protect the people together.
Let's lose our heads for justice and the people together.
You look beautiful today.
I'm going back to my sect.
I just said goodbye to my senior sister.
You're not going to be a police officer anymore?
I still prefer to be free.
Everything is over.
Naturally, I'll return to nature.
Then you
won't come down the mountain anymore?
Before I come out of seclusion next time,
who knows how many months it will be.
Today,
I have to eat my fill of these buns.
Eat.
Delicious, right?
There's something I've always wanted to ask you.
Ask away.
That day at the San Faci Winery,
why did you choose Lin Jinwen to stay with you
instead of me?
Because I still had something to say to him.
What was it?
To tell him
that I forgave him.
But that doesn't mean I'll accept him.
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
To buy you some pineapple cakes.